How does it feel to be fat?
Unwelcome. Heavy. It feels fucking awful. Sweaty. Get smelly more easily.
You're not as flexible without practice. Your penis looks smaller because it's hidden by fat.
You constantly think about food. You think your life would be perfect if you just lost that weight.
But you're drawn to sugar and fat and everything bad. You sometimes eat very little when
with other people so that you can gorge later. You hate yourself when you see the double
chins. You see people stare at you. You dread booths at restaurants. You know people don't respect
you the way they do thin people. You spend half your evenings going to sleep wishing God would
let you die in your sleep because you don't have the guts to do it yourself. Being fat is a
fucking nightmare. I wish I could pay someone to just follow me around all day and slap food out
of my hand. Edit. This is my NSFW account. Please don't click on it. Or you'll see porn. You feel
hated by society. That's the worst part of it. Safe in the knowledge I can't be kidnapped.
It makes you feel bad about yourself and you channel that into your eating.
I'm six feet six and at my heaviest I was 365. I was able to lose 100 pounds over the course of a
year and I was super proud of myself. But when my died died during C19 my good habits went out
the window and I turned back to sugar and food. For comfort, combine that with the fact that I
had been laid off and wasn't being active I was able to gain 55 pounds. Back in a few months
I've since lost some weight and I'm at 295 pounds now. And I'm working my way toward 240.
It's an addiction. In the same way that many people can't get through the day without a few drinks
or a couple joints. Eating is a way for me to deal with stress. Which I have in abundance because of
PTSD. It's a mental addiction rather than physical. Sugar however, is definitely physically addictive.
So much food has sugar in it that it's hard to get away from. Grocery and convenience stores are
designed to tempt you with candy and chocolate at the front. Counter. The other factor for me
is the shame and disgust when I look in the mirror I'm reminded that I'm not where I want to be.
I avoid going to the beach or pool because I don't want to take my shirt off.
I don't like running when people can see me because I look like a cube of jello being shaken.
And every time I have an interaction with someone new my brain tells me that they think I'm
unattractive. I'm a big broad-shouldered guy and after losing so much weight I carry the weight
pretty well. However, the poor self image doesn't go away so easily. Even when I hit my target
that voice will still be in my head. And so will the cravings. It's a constant struggle that
requires willpower and vigilance to overcome. Strangely, other people try to erode that willpower by
telling you that you don't need to lose any weight. That they think you look good. That you're not
even that overweight. First my mom when I was growing up. Then my teachers. Then some friends.
Now it's society trying to say that being fat isn't a bad thing. That you're no less healthier
attractive just because you're overweight. Playing up the delusion that if we learn to love and
accept our fat bodies we won't suffer for it. Down the road. It's bullshit. Just have to keep
working at it. Sad like your body being a jail that you can't get out easily heartbreak.